DEEPASREE A



About Me



- 2 Years experience
- November 25, 1993
- Thikkodi, Kozhikode
- +91.9895079606
- deepasree.a@gmail.com

Python Backend Developer

I intend to pursue a long-term career in a professionally organized sector to learn with the growth of the organization by contributing my best. I will enhance my skills to be competitive, effective, and efficient in the work as well as for organization.



Education

Bachelor, TechnologyCollege of Engineering Vadakara
Cochin University
Kozhikode, Kerala

Graduated, 2011- 2015 First class

+2 KMHSS, Kottakkal

79%, March 2011

10

St. Antonys GHSS, Vadakara

80%, March 2009



Proficiency

- Knowledge of HTML and CSS
- Python
- 4 Github
- 🖶 🛮 Basic knowledge in Django
- Search Engine Optimization(SEO)
- On page Optimization
 - Off page Optimization
 - Google Web master Tool
 - Bing Web master Tool
 - Google Analytics
 - Google Adwords
 - Google Business, Local Listing
 - Sitemap, Blog Posting



Additional Skills

- Basic Knowledge about Servers Like Plesk
- Domain Service like GoDaddy
- Dreamweaver



Work Experience

Currently Doing Internship In Python Djnago from SelfStack (Hilite Business Park)

♣ August 2016– April 2017

SEO ANALYST

Capcee Technologies Ashokapuram kozhikode

NOVEMBER 2015 – JUNE 2016

SEO Trainee

Ellowmedia kozhikode



Works

In SEO

- http://www.greenleavesooty.com/
- http://kottakkalayurveda.ae/
- http://neetexam.in/

All works are done according to selected keywords Site Optimization ,Social Media Management like Facebook Ads creation, Event Posting, Link Building, Blog Creation etc



Languages

- Malayalam
- English



Personality Traits

I'm hardworking, ambitious, capable team player and also capable of learning and adapting to new paradigms.



Personal Details

Father's Name: Mr. Sreedharan A Marital Status: Married Birthday: November 25, 1993 Nationality: Indian

Gender: Female

Declaration

I, Deepasree A, hereby declare that the information contained herein is true and correct to the best of my knowledge and belief.



Thikkodi,Kozhikode May 13, 2023